This is City Traffic Radio.
Welcome, listeners.
We are now broadcasting
real-time traffic conditions.
Why do we have to go so far
for our anniversary?
Are you live-streaming
while driving a ride-hailing car?
It's just a companion stream.
I don't interact.
Why make yourself so tired?
What are you good for?
Driving so slowly.
Mr. Chen,
I don't know what's going on.
The speed just won't go over 100.
Now for a weather update.
In the next three days,
some areas will experience...
This...
You brainless idiot,
do you know how to drive?
Your car broke down too?
What's going on?
Quick, go to that bus ahead.
Get out of my way.
Let me get on first.
Stop looking.
Let's sit in the front.
Welcome to the Master God Bus.
Current stop: Nether Mortuary.
Clearance rules:
1. Survive until dawn.
2. Find and burn
the extremely Yin object of this station.
Those who fail
before the countdown ends...
Who was talking just now?
You heard it too, right?
It's not my hallucination.
What the hell is this place?
Lin Xiaofei, call for rescue immediately.
B-Boss, there's no signal.
Ghost!
What is this ugly thing?
Now you know why I warned you.
It's not human.
What is this?
I don't know. Looks like a zombie.
Like a system,
or a game.
These monsters,
the whole world belongs to him.
Look at your skinny arms and legs.
Why don't you follow me?
I've trained before.
Killed a low-level walking corpse.
EXP +10.
This game experience is quite realistic.
We're even. I don't like owing people.
You hit pretty hard.
Let's get to know each other.
I'm Liu Yiyang.
Xiao Han, forensic doctor.
Don't expect me to thank you.
Don't just stand there.
Anyone who can move, get moving.
Block the windows.
These things eat people.
Staying in the car is waiting to die.
What are you still standing there for?
Go get that box.
Xiao Han, don't just stand there.
Come help.
They are scratching.
What did you say?
Look at their claws.
Although they are attacking,
with their numbers, if they really rammed,
this car would have collapsed long ago.
They are just scratching,
not ramming.
They are slow.
The car won't hold.
Everyone get behind me.
They move slowly.
We can outrun them if we run.
That house is covered in talismans.
It might be a safe zone.
As long as we can get there,
there's still hope.
But it's swarming with these monsters.
How do we get across?
Novice entry procedure complete.
Distributing initial blind box weapons.
What is this junk?
I'm worth tens of millions,
and you give me a megaphone?
Am I supposed to swear
the zombies to death?
What is this junk?
I'm worth tens of millions.
D-Do you know how to use that?
Don't push yourself.
I was on my college Sanda team.
Hide behind me and call me sis.
Don't be afraid, honey.
This is just like the wrench
I use for gas pipes.
Whoever comes near,
I'll twist their head off.
Honey,
didn't you say you'd take me on a trip
after this busy period?
I will. I definitely will once I'm done.
Why doesn't she have a weapon?
It really is a safe zone. Hurry!
Don't get in the way. Hurry!
Bolt the door!
W-What the hell is this place?
Honey, why are your hands so cold?
Don't be afraid.
We're safe inside. I'm here.
A c-coffin? Why is there a coffin here?
The late Master Ren.
Resting unburied,
awaiting joint burial with his late wife.
The guy lying in this coffin
should be worth a lot of points.
At a time like this,
you're still thinking about your points?
If we can't find the item of extreme Yin,
we might all die.
Master Ren inside
should be the item of extreme Yin.
According to the setting,
he'll break out of the coffin tonight.
You've read too many tomb-raiding novels.
Break out of the coffin?
Then we'll fight him to the death.
If we fight head-on
with our current strength,
we'll definitely be wiped out.
We must find something
to seal this coffin tight.